{
    "id": "fa3a0cc36a684c9f98a05e413ac4a20f",
    "title": "Few And Little",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "………………….. people can keep a secret.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "The few",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "fe425dc3e37a4b0eac54ee2d635dcac5"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………. grain that we had was damaged in the rain.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "82e1edb56b36482c8a89b30efd5550f0"
        },
        {
            "question": "She showed …………………. any remorse.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "hardly",
                "hard"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "95d6ef5de6af4896a650d4f49a7f06e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "He spent ………………… . days that were left to him in solitude and meditation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d858f3d2124c486c89a3d05bda3c9a25"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… Jews that live in Kochi have assimilated themselves into the local culture.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "A few",
                "The few"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "889c350d2e364318b5a74006e2794361"
        },
        {
            "question": "We met ……………… Germans during our vacation in Italy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3a450e1ccfa34b3d9b885e55086c2d3f"
        },
        {
            "question": "In ……………… words he expressed his gratitude.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "few",
                "a few",
                "the few"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "75bbfc756e3d498b9a403dda506f7670"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………….. remarks that he made were very provocative.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "A few",
                "The few"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dcec9038ea0f4bbd80e6c5be29466fe6"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………. friends that she has are influential people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Few",
                "A few",
                "The few"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "d44b52fcd25b4e0e9e2880beecaf1739"
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… did he realize what he was getting himself into.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Little",
                "A little",
                "The little"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "4a08f2a9f6804776805cd00ed1aaa60e"
        }
    ]
}